<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://zhhz.cc/sitemap.xsl"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9 http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9/sitemap.xsd" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/</loc>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251105/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-06T12:49:01+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/5/DSC06779.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A highway overpass with a clear blue sky in the background. A green road sign attached to the overpass displays an airplane symbol with the text "Narita" and "E51". Two tall lampposts extend from the overpass, casting minimal shadow. The image captures a section of the overpass structure in shadow on the right.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251106/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-06T21:41:20+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/6/DSC06755.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A small speedboat moves swiftly across deep blue ocean waters, leaving a trail of white wake behind it. The boat, positioned slightly off-center to the right, is angled diagonally toward the top of the image. The water around the boat is textured with small waves and ripples.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251107/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-08T00:14:20+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/7/DSC06692.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Curved highway over water with multiple lanes, elevated train running on upper level, cars on lower levels, surrounded by urban buildings and water reflections.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251108/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-09T00:50:14+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/8/DSC06596-2.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A man and a child stand on a sunlit beach by a calm body of water. The child, wearing a pink dress, reaches towards the man, who is dressed in a black shirt and tan pants. A small black dog sits nearby, while bags and items lie on the sand. The background features a stone wall lining the water.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251109/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-11T00:30:00+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/9/DSC06639-2.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Aerial view of a waterfront with a concrete walkway bordered by a metal railing. Sparkling sunlight reflects on the water's surface. Several people are positioned along the walkway, some engaged in fishing. A bicycle is parked near the grassy area with neatly arranged steps and a lamppost, casting elongated shadows onto the ground.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251110/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-11T00:29:28+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/10/DSC06628.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Steel framework with a grid-like pattern dominates the foreground, casting shadows and lines across the image. A blurred background reveals modern building structures with sunlight illuminating parts of the metal and concrete surfaces. The contrast between light and shadow adds depth to the scene.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251111/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-11T22:58:39+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/11/IMG_1033.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Beam of light cutting through darkness from a row of aligned spotlights, angled downwards, creating sharp contrast in a dark setting. Series of circular holes visible in the background.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251112/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-12T23:51:56+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/12/DSC06820.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Silhouetted city skyline during sunset, featuring tall buildings with visible signs. The sky transitions from deep orange to purple hues. Geometric structure frames the upper corners of the image.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251113/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-13T23:00:18+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/13/DSC06767-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A small boat with a dark hull and an illuminated interior floats on a dark, textured water surface. The boat has several people on board and features a rounded front and an open area on top. Soft warm lighting highlights the boat’s details, contrasting with the surrounding deep blue water.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251114/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-15T01:05:33+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/14/DSC06725.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Black and white urban scene with elevated trains on intersecting tracks, surrounded by tall buildings. Strong shadows create a stark contrast against the structures, highlighting geometric patterns and architectural lines.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251115/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-16T00:30:29+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/15/DSC06666.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Elevated train traveling on a bridge above a river. Below the train, there is a roadway with two visible cars, separated from the train bridge by another structure. The sun creates a lens flare, casting a warm glow on the scene.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251116/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-17T23:32:03+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/27/DSC06643.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Aerial view of three people fishing from a fenced pier jutting out over a large expanse of deep blue water. The pier is angled diagonally across the lower right corner, with one person at the end and two others along the side. Shadows fall across the concrete surface, contrasting with the sunlight.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251117/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-18T00:24:07+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/29/DSC1305.jpeg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Rippling water surface reflecting a blue sky and white clouds, creating a textured, abstract pattern with gentle gradients from blue to white.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251118/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-19T00:59:50+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/30/DSC04759.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Silhouette of a person sitting on the beach facing the ocean at sunset. The sky features vibrant orange and yellow hues with scattered dark clouds. The ocean reflects the colors of the sunset, and the horizon is indistinct against the illuminated sky.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251119/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-20T00:10:17+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/31/DSC05302.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Three tall palm trees rise against a blue sky. A modern, white rectangular building occupies the lower right corner.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251120/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-20T23:08:32+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/32/DSC04998.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Two people stand on a sandy beach, each holding inflatable pink swim rings. A body of water stretches out in front of them, with a large bridge and skyline visible in the background at dusk. The scene is calm, with soft lighting suggesting early evening.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251121/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-22T00:54:32+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/33/R0003459.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[White cylindrical structures with geometric shadows cast by an overhead metal framework. A man stands near one structure with a wheelchair-accessible symbol visible. Sunlit trees in the background create contrast with the architectural elements.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251122/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-23T00:14:42+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/34/DSC06829.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Dimly lit parking area with three yellow and blue traffic barriers labeled "Times" next to a large metal pole. A high fence runs along the background with a blurred train passing by above. The ground has yellow painted lines indicating parking spaces, and a concrete wall is visible behind the fence.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251123/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-24T00:21:20+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/35/DSC06845.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Street underpass at night with brightly lit, colorful mural-covered walls featuring geometric and abstract patterns. Two people walking near a parked car under illuminated street lamps with overhead clearance sign reading 3.6 meters. Dark surroundings contrast the vibrant artwork.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251124/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-25T00:09:32+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/36/R0003449.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A tree with bright yellow leaves stands in the foreground, contrasting against a backdrop of darker trees with red and green foliage. The ground is covered with short, golden grass, suggesting a sunny autumn scene.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251125/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-26T00:13:56+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/37/DSC06879.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Person walking on a shadowed street next to a brightly-lit building with a yellow exterior. The building features a large window displaying colorful posters with Japanese text. A tiled walkway with a yellow tactile guidance path is visible.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251126/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-26T22:54:50+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/38/DSC06865.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Four people stand on a sunlit sidewalk next to a sign with Japanese text. Each person is engrossed in their phone, wearing casual clothing. Shadows create contrasting light and dark areas. The scene suggests a public waiting area.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251127/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-27T23:34:53+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/39/DSC06929.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Golden reeds lit by sunlight, surrounded by lush green tree foliage. Darker background contrasts with the illuminated plants, creating a tranquil natural scene.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251128/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-29T00:43:05+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/40/DSC06935.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Sunset view over a landscape with dense green trees in the foreground, featuring vibrant yellow trees and a cityscape in the middle ground. The background is dominated by gently rolling mountains, softly lit by the setting sun, creating a warm and serene atmosphere.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251129/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-11-29T23:55:51+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/41/DSC06849.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A barbershop interior seen through a partially open door, with a person in a striped shirt attending to a seated customer covered by a white salon cape. "Salon de Ban" is written on the wall, along with stylized Japanese text and a logo featuring a semicircle. Dim, warm lighting gives a cozy ambiance.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251130/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-12-01T00:22:11+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/42/DSC06782.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[City skyline at sunset with high-rise buildings and a red tower. A large body of water in the foreground contains white boats. Several birds fly above the cityscape, and the lighting casts a warm glow on the buildings.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251201/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-12-02T00:46:08+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/43/DSC06957-2.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Brick building with a balcony railing on the left, partially obscured by a cyclist in blurred foreground. Bright yellow autumn leaves fill the upper right, contrasted against a backdrop of green foliage.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251202/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-12-03T00:03:02+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/44/DSC06972.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Vertical white wall with horizontal lines and Hebrew letters spelling "שָׁלוֹם" (shalom) near the center. A vertical metal rod is visible on the left side of the image. The wall appears gently curved, with soft shadows creating rectangular patterns.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/20251203/</loc>
<lastmod>2025-12-03T23:49:13+09:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://zhhz.cc/media/posts/45/R0003455.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Park scene with people relaxing on grass and benches under tall trees with golden autumn leaves. Soft sunlight creates a warm glow, highlighting a group sitting in the foreground on a picnic blanket. Trees and people fill the background, with a lamppost visible at the center.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/page/2/</loc>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://zhhz.cc/page/3/</loc>
</url>
</urlset>